Dibyaranjan Gouda Featured

UI Developer seeking roles in Software Development, Software Design, Requirement Gathering, Application Support, UI

Development, Javascript, React. Js, Angularjs, Bootstrap, Node. Js, Github, CSS, SCSS



Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 2 Month(s)

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Notice Period: Currently Serving Notice Period

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming / Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Electronics/Telecommunication]

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: UI Developer, Software Developer, Software Development, Software Design, Requirement Gathering, Application

Support, UI Development, Javascript, React. Js, Angularis, Bootstrap, Github, CSS, SCSS

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Summary

3.8 years of IT experience as a software developer (UI).

Experience in web application development and integration projects.

Extensively worked on integrating REST APIs developed using spring boot.

Extensively worked on integrating GraphQL developed using spring boot.

Good experience in Front end technologies like JavaScript, HTML and CSS.

Hands on experience in using material UI.

Extensively worked on UI libraries like ReactJS and Redux pattern.

Good knowledge in working B2B platform.

Sound knowledge in web application framework like Angular.

Working experience in the web servers like Tomcat.

Hands on experience on Requirement Analysis, Functional Requirements and handling customer

interactions.

Work Experience

Kredifi Software Pvt. Ltd as UI Developer

Apr 2019 to Dec 2020

Working (Since April 2018)

Client: Kredifi. Team Size: 14+

Employer: Kredifi Software Pvt. Ltd.

Technologies Used:

Front-end: ReactJS and Redux pattern. Material-UI for responsive and styling.

Back-end: Java

Estuate Software as UI Developer

Nov 2016 to Mar 2019

January 2017 to September 2017

Client: Admin license Report.

Team Size: 4

Employer: Estuate Software Pvt. Ltd.

Technologies Used:

Front-end: Angular JS, JavaScript, ¡Query, CSS.

Back-end: NodeJS

October 2017 to March 2018 Client: ASG Technologies.

Team Size: 4

Employer: Estuate Software Pvt. Ltd.

Technologies Used:

Front-end: ReactJS and Redux pattern. Material-UI for responsiveness and styling.

Back-end: Java

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from vignan institute of technology & management in 2015

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
JavaScript			3 Year(s) 8 Month(s)
ReactJS,Redux,NPM, GraphQL			3 Year(s) 5 Month(s)
Angular			
HTML, CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap, Material-UI			3 Year(s) 8 Month(s)
NodeJS, Web Pack			
Apache Tomcat			
Angular, React JS,Node JS			
Github, Bitbucket			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Odia				

Affirmative Action

Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No

Employment Status: Full time

Work Authorization